We'll get back to
the idea of
where the voices in your head come from.
If you don't
remember anything, if, for example, they ask
you, friend, what did you learn last
week,
you can prepare.  You can't
say I don't
remember.  The teacher
said that the voice in your head is
not you.
And you really don't have a
choice about what voices you hear in your
head.  If
you've ever had
depression, if you've ever had a
breakup with a
partner, you know, you can't
tell your mind to stop, to not
talk.
So make yourself comfortable.  And I got used to
this idea.  You don't
control the person who speaks to you.
And it doesn't
matter, because
those
words were spoken before you
heard them.
By then, the speaker had already disappeared
forever.  So, where do these
voices come from?  They come from the green of your
mind.  And these herbs were planted by you.
And no one else can tell you what to
think.  You can't tell yourself what to
think.  Well, others even more so.
If Ganina understands you
,
then the music will be
beautiful and she will
tell you new ideas.  You will be happy for
the rest of your life.
And if you don't learn to control the
process, it will be the
same until
you accidentally send the seeds
.  They don't know that they are sowing
seeds.  And when the grains open, they
have thoughts for their human.
And they have no
control their entire
lives.  You are not
speaking and you have no choice now
which voice will be
heard now.  You have a choice for next
week.
You can sow special greens,
special ones, and that voice will be incredible.
Young people live
better.  Once you know how to sit,
it's
like a pleasure that never
ends and it just keeps getting bigger and
bigger.
I had a company that was
worth a
billion.  I called them 25 years ago.
It was these and that time it was just the
beginning of the
fun and because I knew how much it took
for a cool speaker in my head.  And he always
told me,
"Maybe it would be cool if we
went to worlds again next year."
Okay.
[music] what
you're going to learn this week and
how to do it
I'll go over
the steps and if we have extra
time I'll give you a little headache
we'll
talk about your questions and I'll give you
the answers.  Now we're going to go through all the
pictures because the pictures
help us.  And this is a method that helps you
remember easily.  I know that
Pavel's father is a big fan of
Shanti.  Yes, their
son.  I think they will also have
Buddhist programs to
explain the pictures.
to write the same
pictures.
Next.  So, do we have enough
money?  Let me check.
[music]
What's happening in this
picture?  By the way, by
the way, 50 for what's happening here on
Hype, 50 for what's not happening here.
[music]
The woman in the picture planted the seeds and she
and it grows from
her.  It is represented by a tree.
the seeds she planted in her
mind.  This tree is her
voice.  What doesn't happen on the
catwalk?  She doesn't
eat, she doesn't eat him.  It grows out of it
.
Super.  I'll give you a weird cell because
people like weird cells.
When we think about it
this weekend, just remember this
picture.  I want to
plant and
grow cool things that can be
done.  For example, how I started the
diamond business.
We started with
zama
dollars.  The person in my mind was
very much in the diamond business had a
special.  NDnik.
means I had this voice: "Do it,
do the diamond business."  Do a
diamond
business.  Then
it grew into something incredible.  The largest
diamond company in the world.
So if you develop your voice, it will be
so cool.
[music]
Next
picture.  Maybe you have a pen?
Yes, let's give $100
per
picture.  Yes, don't raise your hand
prematurely.  This picture
represents many of
the choices you don't hear about.   Do
you hear the
best?  You
choose.  By the way, there is a special
system.  He chooses you, and you will
give him 50 of
that.   A
special system to encourage you to have
cool ideas.
Why, instead of putting a bad person in a bad
room, have a bad one.  Oh, okay.  Many
voices you can sow.
Financial
voice, family voice, happy
voice.  With the voice of
healthy good health you can
choose from many
voices.  And I think the voice of
creativity is
the best.  You could say it's a
new kind, a new idea of ​​voice.
Because
you can use this voice on another
pass.  I have a new idea for making
money.  I have a new idea on how to make the
wife cook and clean,
or the
husband.  Think about
this one.  I think my wife has already
processed everything with me.  If you are very
creative, you can be creative in many
different
ways.  In
this
lesson,
we will focus on
creativity.  Yes, don't sweat the
$100.  If you're smart, you've already
raised your hand.
The classroom was turned on.
[music]
clases de cosas que no entiendes.
The best seed for an idea is to go to
classes you don't understand.
Yes,
great.  I don't mean every lesson
that you don't
understand, but it's
so easy, it's so good
advice to go to the classes that we have
every week, they're
free, they're difficult.
It's the hard things that make you
strong.  And don't worry that you
don't
understand anything.  Don't you understand a
single word?  It doesn't matter.  Just
sit there,
listen.  Progress in vain.
It doesn't happen like that
.  He does it, it happens like that
.  This
way, you will have gaps.  You
will burn out.  You will stop walking around
noticeably from meditation.
Meditate, meditate,
meditate.  Watch Netflix, Netflix, Netflix
Netflix.  Then I meditate,
meditate, meditate.  Netflix, Netflix
Disney.  I meditate, meditates,
meditates.  Maybe you're constantly sleeping.   Do
n't even think about
it.  You need to fail somewhere
every
month.  And your patience to not become
angry.  Patience, patience, patience.  And
some guy overtakes you in a car.  You're
like, "Oh you!"
Kala, let's be
stupid again, no one is
perfect.  If you are perfect, you don't
need to come to this
class.  So you
will
fall and expect it and don't get too
disappointed, don't get upset.
Oh my, my meditation is so
bad.  Next picture.  Ready?
[music]
If you don't turn one, you
can use that money on your whole life.
digo con un candado de reloj que tiene
un temporizador para que no puedas abrir
hasta que
ese tiempo que se
ende, the computers seemed to be translating
very quietly, you could not
hear them.  Yes, well done.
Come with me, when I'm
done, I'll give you one of these cases.  I'll
give you
my
class.  It's also
very, very
cool to have on.  This is my
favorite in my life.
I think if you forget to come with me
after the party, it's
okay.  We'll make another one as a T-shirt.
[music]
Okay.  Are you
ready?  Next picture.
[music]
before you
answer.  This is related to the last
picture
in the front.
in order to
live what
Geshen wrote.
Yes, it's a bad answer, but it's the
right answer.
What does this mean?
Before I started the
Goodnight Club
, I stopped reading paper
books because
I stay up
much
later, but I still enjoy
reading
before bed.  If I read on my
phone before bed, I don't
sleep well.  And if I'm reading a paper book
in front of me,
my advice is to
lock it from 10 pm to 6 am.
When I
travel and I'm in my
hotel room, which is a very
unsafe city, I know that I don't trust
myself, so I'll ask my
friend.  He arrives at 10 o'clock.  Suck it,
Rivai.
Okay, yes.
Ah, the computer is okay.  The phone is okay.  I am such a
goodnight.
Good.  Bring the TV remote to
the hotel.
Yes, she sewed.  There are two remotes in your room
.  The
music is absolutely
awful.  I don't
know.  If you stick with this
system, you will double your
productivity.
I said
you can buy eye makeup
or sleep for 8 hours.
Personally,
I think that a woman who slept 5 hours and
uses a lot of Son
Loiret food does not look the same as a
woman who sleeps 8
hours.  8 hours of sleep is very natural.
It is
now the cheapest, cheapest
cosmetics.  You can go to the city, as it is
called, to drink.
Ugh.  I wanted to go to Sofa.
Do some, find some
excuses, don't go
unpunished.  You will save
80 by taking it to the pharmacy.  That lipstick
costs
8 there. I'll come to you.
your face and makes your mind
strong, strong,
powerful.  You won't know unless you
do it.  I'm not saying that one night
you get 8 hours of sleep.
If you do this for three
weeks, your mind will become
stronger and you will feel very
healthy.  I'm a grandfather, I've been going
to classes for 20
years.  Wow!
We just need to
sleep well and get rid of that damn
phone.
Let the phone be with you for 16
hours, and give yourself 8 hours.   Your
phone is supposed to keep your
time, but it takes your
time.  So please, please,
please, please
try.  If you don't have the strength
to do it, find a
friend.  He bought a house near my
house.
He lived thousands of miles from me, and now he lives
two minutes from my
house, when my wife is on
vacation, he knocks around 9 o'clock, walks
to my
house.
Find
another one.  If you're like
me, you don't have the strength to do it on
your own.  You need
friends.  The phone is a lot like
alcohol.  We are all addicted.
What is your favorite place to sit
on your phone?  I like to sit in the bathtub and take a
bath.  My wife in an hour.
Knock-knock-knock-knock.  Yes, you know, there are still
people here who
want to.  Sorry, sorry.  Here is the latest news
about Trump.
So be
careful.  Maybe you don't have the strength
to do it on
your own.  Find a
friend.  Help each
other.  You will never
regret it.  You will be a much more successful
person.  Please.
I was thinking
McDonald's,
Chicken and
something else.
But the next
[music] is
Katynka.
I
like to mix up paper books
and read like that before
bed.  Sometimes I like a really
deep book, and sometimes I read something like
Diamond
Clustering.
Sometimes I feel like I
need something too, sometimes I can read everything by
myself.  So I recommend you have two
books, one more in-depth and one
more relaxing.
You will achieve a deep tone in 6
minutes.  Even in the morning, if you
read it, you will
wake up.  Yes, I didn't show this
picture.  I should have shown it to you yesterday,
but I didn't.
This is the
last one
yesterday.  I told you that there is one special
method to sit really for the
inner
voice.  And, by the way, this man
does just that.
The one in the
green shirt.  La semilla es pensar
[music]
247 para que esté corriendo.
has 24 hours 7 days a week, what
I see is how I planted the past.  I
like it and they have fun for three days.
Chomula didn't teach you a new meditation
because you won't do it and you won't
feel more
free.  I like to feel like I'm the
first.  One says: "I'm tired of everything, don't
teach me any more new meditations."  I
say: "Why?
I already feel the first, that I do not do those
meditations
that you
teach me. And you now, if you teach
another new one, then I will feel even more
pain. Yes. This
, you can do this picture
anywhere. Constant meditation.
Someone might think that he thinks about
the girl. No, not like
that. He thinks, what terms I posted to
meet
this
man. I had a great day.
I was driving in the car and suddenly
Jimi Hendrix music plays. He is so
happy. I was so happy, and then
someone
gave me. Just
think. Do your
meditation. Do a meditation on your
voice with creativity.
What seeds did I post for this
jerk? And then you go to work,
get out of the car, you forget
about it is meditation for one
minute, three times a day, five a day
. Shila. And when should I meditate for 5
hours here, when something is not at all
happens and meditate when something great
happens and think to yourself: "Great, I
met the most amazing people.
Class.  In Mekavit it was so pure.  What did
I
do?  Time.  These are your meditation
triggers.   Is
something bad
happening or is something good
happening?  You ask the question, "Why
me? Why
me?"  My
teacher taught me in various strange
ways.   I have to
clean the toilet every day, I have to learn
something.  So, he bought a
TV.  He
said, "I'm the boss of the monastery and I can
watch TV, but you can't."
And he said,
"Well, if there's anything interesting on
TV, I'll ring the
bell."  Well, have you ever wondered why
those tall lamas have bells?  They were
calling to their
TV.  So you hear the bell and run around the
warehouses with
your foot on the TV?
okay,
okay.  I was constantly sitting next to
my running leg
.  I'm watching
the news.  And there was news that someone's house had burned down
.  She left the house alone and it healed
.  She is
crying.  Why me?  Why
me?  Many people do that.  Why me?  Why
me?  Why did my house burn down?  He
said: "That's it, maybe you still
have it."  So
why?  What are you?  What?  I said:
"I'll come back to
where I left off, I'll work again in about an
hour.
"  He says:
"Look, there's this
handsome guy on
TV knocking on the doors of poor
people from New York."
Knock-knock-knock-knock-knock.  The lady answers.   The
old lady opens the door.  And he says, "You're the
lottery winner."
Here are 5
million. And they
loved to say videos.
She dances like that.
And he asks
me why she didn't ask that question
.  Nobody says why
me, when your house is ruined, everyone is like, "Why
me, why me, why me?"
And if you're constantly the creative
voice, you'll say, "Why me all the
time? Who ever has something bad
happen to them?
It's natural to say, why me."  But also
when something good
happens.  Why
me, by the way?
[music]
Have you noticed that I'm not telling you what to
think?  I just want you to ask
questions.  How you answer
this question is up to
you, it's your
problem.  I'm just asking you to ask
questions.  Is something good happening?
something bad is
happening.  Why
me?  You
answer
yourself.  I don't think this meditation
takes longer than two or three
minutes because your life is
moving.  You can't sit for two
hours and wonder why you have some kind of
undercut.
We don't have
time.  I want you to ask me for
at least 30
seconds.  You will be responsible.  You know it's
your size.  I don't
know.  So, let's get back to serious
money
matters.  I know the following picture.  And that's it, the
money ran out.
But you don't need to
be
careful now.  Why me?  Super well
done.
Yes, I was reviewing the reading.  Now
let's see if
we have time.   there
are.  Yes, we will make short excerpts from
the readings so you can
get a feel for what it's about
.  And then we'll end with questions and
answers.  I read nada on you
.  Yes, let's go for a
walk today.
Ntolto
so easy to read.  No, don't be, don't
stay
here.  Yes, come on, nice.
By
the way, he is the best teacher, a teacher of the
Tibetan language.
He teaches three lessons every
week.  20. Oh, okay.
If you don't come to this
class, they're free, they're fun.
He knows how to train people to be
faster than
me.  Don't be shy, come to class.
Here is the translation of
It's about the pen.
pen.
If this pen comes from itself,
it will never
change, it will never
end in a draft.
If the pen comes from itself, from
the pen, the ink will never run out,
if the pen comes from
me, if the pen comes from my
greens.  Every time I use a
pen, and I'm going
to change it now.  What is your name?  Aha.
It's blowing.  Every time you use a
pen, ink
is discharged.  This is not ink
being written out.  Your
grains.  You use your
seeds.  There is no more money.  So, where is
my
bank?  Come on, more.
You'll explain to my wife where the money went.
Big question.  A difficult
question.  When you write with
pens and you write
what, where does the writing come from?
Don't think, don't raise your hand like that.
Lift
high.  You
do it for money.  The smell is similar to mine.  Yes,
okay.
Sla.  People
say the
pen exists on its own side.  I
say, "Why?"
And they say, "She can write on
paper."  But
the writing doesn't come from the
pen.  When you move
the pen, your
hand creates writing on the
paper.  Welcome to your bad news.  Why?
Every minute, the next moment of
the film comes from
somewhere,
I want
to see a new move.
By the way, in my meditative questions, you
can go to the movie and
meditate.  Such a strange guy.  What can I
do?  Who
wrote the movie?  You wrote the
movie.  A new picture appears every second
.  This is your mind
creating.  Don't
forget.  Things are
steaming.
Why?  When some movies end, are you
that happy?
I'm like,
this movie is over
.  I have a feeling I should
wait until the end because I
paid money, but I don't like the
movie.  And when the movie ends, I'll still
say I'm glad the movie
is over.  Why did the movie end?
they finished the taichika dream of your body
also your body was created inside
your
mother by the way
you start with the chakras first next to each other
then the channels and then the bones around the
channels and then the
lo.  And
this is for
weeks in your
mother's womb, but then everything grows together.
It all comes from your
tan
and when you use your price,
it ends.
Well, there's no reason why it should
end in black.
If the pen is on the
loose
side, it will never end up in a draft.
He
always builds, but if he comes from
you, he is like
that.  Yes, one more question.  Maybe we
have a position Yes, yes?  Everyone probably spends
all their
phone in this
book of
poetry.  This is a discussion, this is a struggle between
two
people,
between man and the
devil.  Sometimes poetry
speaks, and sometimes poetry is spoken by
the devil, who speaks this, this,
this fraction of 100. And why?   The
angel
[music]
speaks because he creates his own
life.  Yes, because the angel explains why
you are getting older.
She explains to Mr. Angel why your
relationship
is ending.  This is general advice.
100 and we move on to the question of
the answer.  Maybe Oscar will come, he's
incredible.
He is one of the best.  I didn't hear anything
in this child's room.  Can you
read here?  Yes.
[music]
también se volvería More
Okay.
Good.  If things don't go well
, nothing
can
be
my
money or yours.  And there can be none and your
tummy cannot be yours.
Your home cannot be
yours.  Your wife or husband cannot
be yours.  Children cannot be
yours if they are not from Zaren.
Things that don't belong
can never be yours.
Things that don't belong can never
be
yours.  Yes, it will be
deep now.  Things that do not originate
can never be related to other
things.
Have my grandson.
You say you have after this child,
but if there is no charge, there can be no
connection.  If Maitri originates in
himself, he cannot originate from his mother.
Only things that come from design can
come from other
people.
If it comes from itself, I
can never own
it, because it does not come from my
heart.
also comes from
ours.  If I lose my memory, it also
comes from
mine.  If things come from my distant past,
they never
fade.  If things are by design,
no one can have them.  You need to think about this
.
[music] A
world that does not
originate is not
possible.  A pen that doesn't come out can't
run out of
ink.  When you need a pen and your
friend gives it to you.
Sometimes you need a pen and you
go to the store and they say,
"Excuse me, pens are out. You don't get
pens from stores, you get pens from
grains. You need to
share what you have. Then you'll
get more."
Jesus repeated it again and again.
Jesus, Master Zelen is so cool
.  He said all the time: "What do you
want, yes, give it to others."
Someone asks, someone will come to your
house, find out their phone number and
call them, say, maybe you still
need a
raincoat, you're on the hook.  You say, "Oh, this one
will hit well too."  Only Master Zarin would
say that.  Rob is ready.
We have
enough field work to go home.  But we
have a
credit card.  Who wrote this
part?  I want the correct answer.  Not that
I wrote them.  Is this an angel speaking
or
not and why?
Yes, but never answer
questions that are paid for with a
question mark.   An
angel must be an
angel.  Why?
Because he comes from
mine.
Remember the picture of the girl from Flenna?
Grains, if they're talking about
grains, if it's about grains, it
must be an angel.  The devil doesn't
like that.  Where is she?
Good.  The last one.
I think it would be cool if Gipson
stood up and
read it.  Gipson is a very, very cool
translator in Taiwan.
I don't know what he's doing here in Mexico
City, but I'm
[music]
happy.  I also wanted to congratulate his
partner Emilya.
Gibson specializes in what we
call pocket books.  He has already
hung two.
They are 60 years old.
And the idea was that there were these little
books that you could carry in your
handbag.
There is
Word's translation, there is Tim's translation.  And
they are useful when you are having sex with your
husband.
They are very
heavy, such big
books.  I'm going to hit you right now
.  But Gipson's specialization is
small.  We call
these books for cats.
He is currently working on his third, he will finish the
cake. He has been helping the team for many years,
which raises
money to help the
Gadalhai parade team.
to help refugees
who are reaching South America
.  And they have such a nice
little house there, where people can
wash, rest, and
eat.  Yes.
Then they are
again
the top.  And
this project doesn't last 10 years.
[music]
Don't worry, I won't
ask,
but for the people of Taiwa, the team is giving them this
box.  And that's how we raised a lot of
money.
They also support the team that
translates these books at
One more
time.  Thank you.  Thank you for your hard
work.
Thank you for
your tireless
work.  Ada will then read it in Spanish
and we have minus minutes.  Yes.
Lead people by the hand
to nothing at all.  Teach them not to think
about anything.  Make them concentrate.
Sorry, I didn't have time to read it.  They don't read
English like that.  Now I will explain.
If you
are going to join the team of
Latin
American teachers, chair
Zalda, you can speak this
way.  What will you do in Costa Rica?
What will you
teach?  Oh, we will take people by the
hand, we will lead them into
nothingness.
Next, we will teach them a special
meditation.  Don't think about anything
.  Yes.
Next, we will teach them, when they
meditate, to think about as many objects
as you
can.  We will make them
true imitation
masters.  Who is speaking?
K
Blocks
dew.  Oh, how I love them.
[laughter]
People ask me, Gresha, you haven't
been to Mecca for so
long?  Why did you leave again?
Because I
remembered when I went to
see the big
cauldron, there were cherries right next to it
.  I always want to go to this
church.  Thank you.
saw the next one